<resources>
    <string name="app_name1">Hangboarder Helper</string>
    <string name="app_name">Hangboarder Helper</string>
    <string name="new_workout">Created Workout</string>
    <string name="exercise_1">exercise_1</string>
    <string name="exercise_2">exercise_2</string>
    <string name="exercise_3">exercise_3</string>
    <string name="exercise_4">exercise_4</string>

    <string name="button_add_new_text">Add new</string>
    <string name="button_delete_row_description">Delete</string>
    <string name="TestButtonName">save</string>
    <string name="TestButtonName2">load</string>
    <string name="generateWorkoutName">generate workout</string>
    <string name="addWorkoutName">Add Workout</string>
    <string-array name="categories">
        <item>10/5 Repeater</item>
        <item>7/3 Repeater</item>
        <item>5/5 Repeater</item>
        <item>Max Hang</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="PreRunOptions">
        <item>RUN</item>
        <item>EDIT</item>
        <item>RETURN</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="infotext"><![CDATA[
    <b>What is Hangboarding?</b><br/>
Hangboarding is an effective method of rock climbing training which involves performing repeated deadhangs in particular grip configurations, for particular intervals.
It develops isometric grip strength specific to whatever kind of holds are desired, and can be easily tailored to address a climber\'s individual weaknesses or goal routes.<br/><br/>
<b>When should I hangboard?</b><br/>
If you climb regularly and feel you have plateaued at a particular level of max-effort moves or sequences, hangboarding could be a great way to continue improving.
Also, if you feel that for example your crimp strength is lagging behind your sloper strength, hangboarding is one way to specifically develop your crimp strength.<br/>
HOWEVER, hangboarding is a high intensity exercise and it can be RISKY. It places a great deal of strain on your tendons, and you must be vigilant and careful not to
overdo it. As a rule of thumb, you should be comfortably sending V5 before attempting to hangboard - newer climbers do not have the prerequisite tendon strength to
safely hangboard, and would be better served to train by bouldering. That being said, a careful climber will see huge strength gains from hangboarding!<br/><br/>
<b>How to use this app:</b><br/>
This app is designed to help you design and follow a consistent hangboarding routine to maximize the benefit you get from training. Press the (+) button to add a workout,
then add 6-8 exercises to it, each named as the intended grip (ex: medium crimp). Beginners should perform 10/5 repeaters, which are 10 seconds under tension and 5 seconds
rest, repeated 6 times in 90 seconds. Your first time through the workout, you will see that you need to add or subtract weight from your bodyweight in order to complete
each exercise - record this after each exercise, and it will be stored for next time.
    ]]></string>
</resources>